Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Campus Buildings
  - Washington Square Book Center (Bookstore), 1938-1984 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Students Looking at Books, Aisle 1, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5849; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 36)
    - Students in Front of the New York University Book Center Entrance, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5851; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 37)
    - Women Leaving the New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5853; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 38)
    - Students in an Aisle, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5855; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 39)
    - Security Guards, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5857; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 40)
    - Basement Cashier, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5859; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 41)
    - Book Display, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5861; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 42)
    - Registers, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5863; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 43)
    - Two Students in Front of Book Tables, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5865; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 44)
    - Basement of New York Univeristy Bookstore, Looking Towards Information Desk, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5867; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.75 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 45)
    - Cashier, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5869; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 46)
    - Basement Aisle, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5871; Imperatore, India; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 47)
    - Basement Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5873; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 48)
    - Information Desk, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5875; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 49)
    - Empty Shelves, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5877; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 50)
    - Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; xNYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5879; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 51)
    - Basement Security Camera, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5881; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 52)
    - Basement Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5883; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 53)
    - Checkout Lines, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5885; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 54)
    - Cashier, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5887; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 55)
    - Barnes and Noble Bookstore, 5th Avenue at 18th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5889; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 56)
    - Security Camera Monitors, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5891; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 57)
    - Information Desk, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5892; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 58)
    - Entrance Turnstiles, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5895; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 59)
    - Set Your Own Price Book Display, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5897; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 60)
    - Display of George Orwell Works, New York University Bookstore, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5899; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 61)
    - Strand Bookstore, 828 Broadway at 12th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5901; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 62)
    - Entrance, New York University Book Center, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5903; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 63)
    - All Shoplifters Will Be Prosecuted Sign, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5905; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 64)
    - Shoplifter Arrested for Stealing Books, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5907; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 65)
      Crime and criminals; New York University -- Buildings
    - Shoplifter being Arrested, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5909; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 66)
    - Shoplifter being Arrested, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5911; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 67)
    - Security Mirror, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5913; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 68)
    - Shelving Books, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_re5915; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 69)
    - Entrance, New York University Bookstore, 18 Washington Place, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5917; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 70)
    - Merchandise Display, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5919; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 71)
    - Modeling Merchandise, New York University Bookstore, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5921; color print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 72)
  - Breevort Hotel, circa 1890-1948 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Brevort Hotel, 15 5th Avenue at 8th 9th Street, circa 1948; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5924; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Brevort Hotel, 15 5th Avenue at 8th Street, circa 1890; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5926; black-and-white print (photograph), 10 x 13 inches (Box 186, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Exteriors, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5927 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Corner of Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5952; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Awning, Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5932; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Student in Front of Brittany Resident Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5934; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Entrance, Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5936; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Brittany Residence Hall, Looking North, 55 East 10th Street at Broadway, 1966; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5938; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Brittany Residence Hall, 55 East 10th Street, 1965; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5940; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Brittany Residence Hall, Looking West, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5942; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Folder 7)
    - Entrance, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5944; color print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 4, Item 8)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Broadway Windows, Undated (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Sculpture by Ming Fay in Broadway Windows, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5947; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 5, Item 1)
      Art.; New York University -- Buildings
    - Sculpture by Ming Fay in Broadway Windows, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5949; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Brittany Residence Hall - Interiors, 1968-1984 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - View of Entrance Security Desk from Inside the Elevator, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5952; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4.5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Burglary Scene, Room 604, Brittany Residence Hall, 1980; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5954; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - Meeting, Brittany Residence Hall, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5956; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Meeting, Brittany Residence Hall, 1981; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5958; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 4)
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5960; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 5)
      Dwellings.; New York University -- Buildings
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5962; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 6)
    - Room 303, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5964; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 7)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5966; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 8)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5968; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 9)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5969; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 10)
    - Room 1400, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5972; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 11)
    - Student Studying, Room 907, Brittany Residence Hall, 1984; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5974; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 12)
    - Three Students, Brittany Residence Hall, circa 1968; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5976; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 13)
    - Two Students, Brittany Residence Hall, 1968; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5978; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 14)
    - Two Students, Brittany Residence Hall, 1968; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5980; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 15)
    - Students and Beds, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5982; black-and-white print (photograph), 5.5 x 8.5 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 16)
    - Students and Beds, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5983; black-and-white print (photograph), 5.5 x 8.5 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 17)
    - Fire Sprinkler System, Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5986; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 18)
    - Lounge (Villa Marbona), Brittany Residence Hall, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5988; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 186, Folder 6, Item 19)
  - Bronfman Center, Undated (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Drawing of Exterior, Bronfnam Center, NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5991; color print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 186, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Drawing of Exterior, Bronfman Center, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5993; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Two Students in the Library, Bronfman Center, Undated; NYU_ARCH_PHOTO_00001_ref5995; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - 715 - 725 Broadway (TSOA Building), 1964-1983 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - View of Building from Washington Pl. and Broadway, Street Level, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6004; Black and White Print, (photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - 725 Broadway, Building Facade, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6005; Black and White print (photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6011; Black and White print, (photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North, February 1, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6013; Black and White print, (photograph) 8 x 10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - 725 Broadway, Detail of Arch, Columns and Windows, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6015; Black and White print, (photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 5)
      Art.; Architecture; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - 721 Broadway, Tisch Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6018; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 6)
      Architecture; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
    - 721-725 Broadway, New Tisch School of Arts (TSOA) Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6020; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5 x 8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 7)
    - 721 Broadway, Warner Communications, 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6022; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 8)
    - 725 Broadway, Building Entrance, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6024; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 9)
    - 719-721 Broadway, Building Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6026; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 10)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North West, April 16, 1970; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6028; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 11)
    - 725 Broadway, Waverly Place Street View, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6030; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 12)
    - 721 Broadway, Unauthorized Persons Will Be Subject To Criminal Trespass (sign), undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6032; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - 721 Broadway, Warner Communications Building, February 1981; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6034; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 14)
    - 721 Broadway, Front of Building Window with Student Performance Poster (vertical), April 19, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6036; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 15)
    - 721 Broadway, Front of Building Window with Student Performance Poster (horizontal), April 19, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6038; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 16)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking West on Washington Place, May 22, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6040; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 17)
    - 725 Broadway, Looking North West, May 22, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6042; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 8, Item 18)
  - Brown Building
    - Brown Building, Corner of Greene and Washington Place Looking North West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6047; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x7 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 1)
      Architecture; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings; New York University -- Real property
    - Brown Building, Aerial view of Corner of Greene and Washington Place from Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6049; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - Brown Building, 29 Washington Place, West Side of Greene Street Looking North from Washington Place, April 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6051; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 3)
    - Brown Building, 29 Washington Place, West Side Corner of Greene Street Looking North From Washington Place, April 1947; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6053; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 4)
    - Triangle Fire Plaque on Brown Building, April 27, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6055; Black and White print, (Photograph) 5x7 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 5)
    - Brown Building, Ceremony in Council Room with Mr. Frederick Brown, Mrs Frederick Brown, Dr. William H. Nichols, Vice President of the Council, and Chancellor Elmer Ellsworth Brown (left to right), April 22, 1929; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6057; Black and White print, (Photograph) 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 6)
    - Brown Building, Corner of Greene Street, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6060; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 7)
    - Brown Building, seen from Greene Street and Washington Place intersection, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6062; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 8)
    - View of Washington Pl. from the Brown Building between Greene St. and Washington Square Place, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6064; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 9)
    - Washington Square North looking down from the Brown Bldg., undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6066; Black and White print (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 10)
    - Frederick Brown Building Plaque, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6068; Black and White print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 11)
    - Brown Building, Washington Square North, Washington Place at Greene Street, March, 26, 1984; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6071; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 12)
      Architecture; New York University -- Buildings; New York University -- Real property; New York University. Washington Square Campus
    - Henry James Plaque, Brown Building, March 10, 1967; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6073; Black and White print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 186, Folder 9, Item 13)
  - Brown Building - Biology and Chemistry Laboratories, 1969
    - Cell Biology Research Center New York University, Artist's Rendering, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6077; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Brown Building Chemistry Lab, Room 553, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6079; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Brown Building Biology Lab, Room 601, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6081; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Carter Hall
    - Arthur L. Carter Hall, 10 Washington Place, Building Facade, 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6083; Prince, James; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Arthur L. Carter Hall, 10 Washington Place, Front Door Molding Detail, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6085; Pellettieri, Luigi; Black and White Print, (Photoraph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center
    - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center, Computer-Generated Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6089; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 7x5 inches (Box 187, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6091; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Cantor Film Center Dedication with Norman F. Cantor, Alec Baldwin and Spike Lee., undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6093; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 3, Item 3)
      Lee, Spike; Baldwin, Alec, 1958-; Cantor, Norman F.; New York University. Washington Square Campus; New York University -- Buildings
  - Casa Italiana
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southwest, Watercolor, 1990; UA_PHOTO_001_REF6140; Color Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southeast, Watercolor, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6142; Color Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking South, Drawing, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6144; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 3 1/2x 5 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Southwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6146; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6148; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Casa Italiana, Winfield Scott House National Historic Landmark Plaque, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6150; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Casa Italiana, Looking Up At Windows, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6152; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Casa Italiana, Auditorium, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6154; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - Chemistry Building, Artist's Rendering
    - Chemistry Building, Johnson and Foster, Sketch, January 26, 1970; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6157; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Clinton Hall, Beekman and Nassau Streets
    - Clinton Hall with Carriages and Pedestrians, The First Home of the University, Sketch, April 13, 1956; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6160; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Clinton Hall with Carriages and Pedestrians, Sketch, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6162; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x9 1/4 inches (Box 187, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Clinton Hall, Sketch, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6164; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 187, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Catholic Center
    - Catholic Center Site, Thompson Street and Washington Square South, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6095; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x6 1/2 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Catholic Student Center, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6101; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Aerial View of Catholic Center, Loeb and Shimkin, Looking East, October 2, 1959; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6103; Simmons, William R.; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Catholic Center, Washington Square South, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6105; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Catholic Center, Stained Glass and Steeple, circa 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6107; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 187, Folder 4, Item 5)